<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:15:25 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PicoCTF_2023</title>
      <link>/posts/picoctf_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:15:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/picoctf_2023/</guid>
      <description>Binary Exploitation tic-tac Someone created a program to read text files; we think the program reads files with root privileges but apparently it only accepts to read files that are owned by the user running it. ssh to saturn.picoctf.net:62983, and run the binary named &amp;ldquo;txtreader&amp;rdquo; once connected. Login as ctf-player with the password, d137d16e
Upon ssh into machine, we see txtreader binary and flag.txt file, however we don&amp;rsquo;t have permissions to read them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NahamConCTF_2023</title>
      <link>/posts/nahamconctf_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:41:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nahamconctf_2023/</guid>
      <description>Warmup Fast Hands Author: @JohnHammond#6971
You can capture the flag, but you gotta be fast!
We are given a button to Capture The Flag:
Clicking the button opens a new window that closes rather abruptly. The challenge prompt suggests we be quick, so I am thinking a curl request might be good since the contents do not close. Right clicking does not, however, allow me to copy a link url. I decided to see how this action is behaving when redirected through burp:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N00bzCTF_2023</title>
      <link>/posts/n00bzctf_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:25:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/n00bzctf_2023/</guid>
      <description>Misc Amazing Song Lyrics This is a wierd png file. I hope you can make some sense out of it!
Note: Wrap the flag in n00bz{} and flag is all lowercase Author: NoobMaster The image is a pictogram for certain sign languages, but what language? I am no expert in sign language so I begin with random google searching. A brief search for American Sign Language alphabet gives me hand shapes that look similar:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox_Cyber_Apocalypse_2023</title>
      <link>/posts/hackthebox_cyber_apocalypse_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 19:01:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hackthebox_cyber_apocalypse_2023/</guid>
      <description>Forensics Extraterrestrial Persistence There is a rumor that aliens have developed a persistence mechanism that is impossible to detect. After investigating her recently compromised Linux server, Pandora found a possible sample of this mechanism. Can you analyze it and find out how they install their persistence? Difficulty: very easy
For this challenge we are provided with a small persistence.sh script. Within the code, we see base64 encoded information being directed to a file service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trophies</title>
      <link>/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:43:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/</guid>
      <description>CTFs Nahamcon 2023 74th place out of 2522! My contribution was 3749 points out of the team&amp;rsquo;s 7425 :)
HTB Cyber Apocalypse 2023 118th place out of 6483 participating teams!
Hackthebox HTB Seasons Beta I Achieved Platinum Rank in HTB Seasons Beta I. All Easy, Medium and Hard challenges were completed within a week of release except for 1 Hard difficulty machine.
Achieved Pro Hacker Rank After completing 14/20 active boxes, I earned Pro Hacker rank on HTB</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
